Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum I
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum I
1983-2006
RG 11I
Yale University Divinity School Library
13
(31 boxes)
This record group represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping the papers in record groups 11, 11A, 11B, 11C, 11D, 11E, 11F, 11G, and 11H. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board lent its support. The United Board was established to support and coordinate the activities of Protestant colleges and universities in China and after 1950 extended its work to other parts of Asia.
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the UBCHEA, 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia was established in the 1920s to support and coordinate the activities of Protestant colleges and universities in China. Following the Communist takeover of China, the United Board focused its efforts on educational work in other Asian nations. In recent years it has re-focused some of its activities on China. See the annual reports of the United Board for a detailed description of program activities during the period covered by this collection.
Scope and Contents
The files have been maintained as sent by the United Board.
Arrangement
I:
Administrative Records
II:
Program Grants
III:
Financial Records
Universities and colleges -- China; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
- Administrative Records, Series I
  - Board of Trustees annual meeting actions, 1987-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees annual meeting actions, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1992 Nov (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1993 Apr (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1993 Apr (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1993 Nov (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1993 Nov (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1995 Apr (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1995 Nov (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1995 Nov (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1996 Apr (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1996 Apr (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1996 Nov (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1997 Apr (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1997 Nov (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1998 Apr (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1998 Nov (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1998 Nov (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1999 Apr (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1999 Apr (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1999 Nov (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 1999 Nov (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2000 Apr (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2000 Apr (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2000 Nov (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2000 Nov (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2001 Apr (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2001 Apr (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees minutes, 2001 Apr (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee actions, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee actions, 1995-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - China Concerns Subcommittee minutes, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - China Programs Subcommittee minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - East Asia and Intra Asia Subcommittee minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Nomination Subcommittee minutes, 1991-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Personnel Resources Subcommittee minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Personnel Resources Subcommittee minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Program Policy Subcommittee minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Program Policy Subcommittee minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Program Policy Subcommittee minutes, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - South and Southeast Asia Subcommittee minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - University Programs Subcommittee minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - University Programs Subcommittee minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Women's Concerns Subcommittee minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Women's Concerns Advisory Subcommittee minutes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Development Committee minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Development Committee minutes, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Development Committee minutes, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Development Committee minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Investment Committee minutes, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Investment Committee minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Investment Committee minutes, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Asian Institute materials, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Asian Institute materials, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - China Committee minutes, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - China Committee minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - China Committee minutes, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - China Committee minutes, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - East and Intra Asia Program Committee minutes, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - East and Intra Asia Program Committee minutes, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - East and Intra Asia Program Committee minutes, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - South and Southeast Asia Committee minutes, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - South and Southeast Asia Committee minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - South and Southeast Asia Committee minutes, 2001 Nov (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - South and Southeast Asia Committee minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - South and Southeast Asia Committee minutes, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Program Grants, Series II
  - Cambodia
    - Royal University of Phnom Penh
      - Proposal/grant/report, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Steven Boswell, visiting professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Sub-grant to Ateneo de Manila for RUPP scholars, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - East Timor
    - National University of Timor Lorosae
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - India
    - India Program Review
      - Reviews/reports, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 4)
        Scope and Contents
        Madras Christian College- UB Review Team visit, Madras Christian College Response, Madras School of Economics, Stella Maris College
      - Surveys/reports, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        Social Sciences in South India, Women's Christian College report, Educational Policies influencing Indian Higher Education, Women in Higher Education
      - United Board India Program Review, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - All India Advisory Committee on Higher Education
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Clifford and Kathleen Hill/ AIACHE Seminar, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Anniyil Ninan Tharakan, professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Anniyil Ninan Tharakan, professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Ahmednagar College
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - American College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report and special grant, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Arul Anandar College
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Christ College
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Workshop on Information Technology for Educational Administrators in Higher Education, 2002 Apr (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Workshop on Information Technology for Educational Administrators in Higher Education, 2002 Apr (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Workshop on Information Technology for Educational Administrators in Higher Education, 2002 Apr (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Workshop on Information Technology Librarians in Higher Education, 2002 May (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report/course material, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report/course material, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Workshop on Best Practices in Administration of Higher Educational Institutions, 2003 May (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Henry Martyn Institute of Islamic Studies
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Holy Cross College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Isabella Thoburn College
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - grant agreement for UB fellow, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Lady Doak College
      - Nirmala Jeyeraj, visiting scholar file, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - proposal/ special grant, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Madras Christian College
      - grant report, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - grant report, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - grant report, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - grant report, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - proposal/correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant with additional discretionary grant, 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Mar Thoma College, Tiruvalla
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - report, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - report, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Saint Ann's College, Mangalore
      - grant reports, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Saint Anthony's College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Saint Christopher's College of Education
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Saint John's College, Agra
      - proposal/ grant, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Saint Joseph's College, Bangalore
      - proposals/grants/reports and correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Saint Joseph's College, Tiruchirapali
      - proposals/reports, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Saint Thomas College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Saint Xavier's College, Ahmedabad
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Saint Xavier's College, Palaymkottai
      - correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Serampore College
      - correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - proposals/grants/reports, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Stella Maris College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Union Christian College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - grant- FLDSP, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - University of Madras
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Wilson College
      - correspondence, 1984-1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - The Women's Christian College
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - proposal/grant, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - grant- FLDSP, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia
    - Artha Wacana Christian University
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - BAKOR- Coordinating Board for Christian Education Foundations in Indonesia
      - proposal/grant/report- library project, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Indonesia Project administered by Satya Wacana
      - proposals/grants, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Indonesian Graduate Program of Theology
      - correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Nommensen University
      - proposal/grant/reports, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Petra University
      - grant report, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Ann E. Robinson, visiting professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Satya Wacana University
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Japan
    - International Christian University
      - grant reports/ correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Tokyo Union Theological Seminary
      - proposals/grants/reports, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Korea
    - Ewha Womans University
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - proposal/grant, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - proposal/grant, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant + 3 smaller grants, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - proposal/grant + 3 smaller grants, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Sook-Ja Chun, visiting professor file, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Hannam University
      - proposal/grant, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Seoul Women's University
      - grant/report, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - proposal/grant, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - proposal/grant/report, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - proposal/grant/report, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 10)